{  
  "Questions":[  
     {  
        "Question":"Who was the first player drafted in the first NFL draft in 1936?",
        "Answers":[
            "Bart Starr",
            "Jay Berwanger",
            "Don Hutson"
        ],
        "Answer":"1"
     },
     {  
        "Question":"In 1993, what NFL team made off-season trades for Joe Montana and Marcus Allen?",
        "Answers":[
            "Kansas City Chiefs",
            "Denver Broncos",
            "Oakland Raiders"
        ],
        "Answer":"0"
     },
     {  
        "Question":"What team won 3 Super Bowls in the 1990s?",
        "Answers":[
            "Broncos",
            "Patriots",
            "Cowboys"
        ],
        "Answer":"2"
     },
     {  
        "Question":"Who was the first player to rush for 1000 yards in a season?",
        "Answers":[
            "Jim Brown",
            "Joe Perry",
            "Beattie Feathers"
        ],
        "Answer":"2"
     },
           {  
        "Question":"Which NFL team features a helmet logo on only one side of their helmet?",
        "Answers":[
            "Steelers",
            "Dolphins",
            "Patriots"
        ],
        "Answer":"0"
     },
           {  
        "Question":"What wide receiver caused a sensation his rookie season with a one-handed catch?",
        "Answers":[
            "Jerry Rice",
            "Randy Moss",
            "Odell Beckham, Jr"
        ],
        "Answer":"2"
     },
           {  
        "Question":"Who holds the best rookie passer rating in NFL history?",
        "Answers":[
            "Dan Marino",
            "Steve young",
            "Dak Prescott"
        ],
        "Answer":"2"
     },
           {  
        "Question":"What is the oldest NFL franchise in continuous operation with the same name in the same location?",
        "Answers":[
            "Dallas Cowboys",
            "Green Bay Packers",
            "Chicago Bears"
        ],
        "Answer":"1"
     },
                 {  
        "Question":"What Motown singer tried out for the Detroit Lions in 1970?",
        "Answers":[
            "Marvin Gaye",
            "Smokey Robinson",
            "Lionel Richie"
        ],
        "Answer":"0"
     },
                 {  
        "Question":"Which player holds the NFL record for longest interception return?",
        "Answers":[
            "Ronnie Lott",
            "Ed Reed",
            "Deion Sanders"
        ],
        "Answer":"1"
     }     
  ]
}
